question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Super Mario Bros. was released in 1990.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Half-Life&quot; series, &quot;H.E.V&quot; stands for &quot;Hazardous Evasiveness Vest&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Cave Crawler&quot; will attack you.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
